

Mikhael Bradley Soebroto

Senior Computer Science Student at Seattle Pacific University

ABOUT ME

Hi, My name is Mikhael Bradley Soebroto and I am 19 Years Old. I am currently working towards my Bachelors Degree in Computer Science at Seattle Pacific University. I am currently a Senior year and was transferred over from Edmonds College. I want to work in this position to gain experience and learn new things.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Edmonds College

Edmonds, Washington Associate's Degree in Computer Science 2020-2022

- Java, HTML/CSS, Python, JavaScript
- Vice President of Edmonds Indonesian Club
- Vice President of Edmonds Computer Science Club

Seattle Pacific University

Seattle, Washington Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science 2022-2024 (Expected)

- Direct Transfer Degree Scholarship Recipient
- Transfer Merit Scholarship Recipient

WORK EXPERIENCE

XecureIT

Jakarta, Indonesia Cybersecurity Intern July 2023 - September 2023

- Java, HTML/CSS, Javascript, MongoDB
- Built Plugins for Log Management System
- Monitored Servers and Firewalls
- Learned the backbone Infrastructure of a cybersecurity ecosystem

VOLUNTEER WORK

First Aid Volunteer & Ticketing Supervisor Premiere Cup Committee 2017-2019

- · Managing ticket sales and accounting
- Manage Human Resources in the Ticketing Division
- Worked under stressful condition as a Red Cross Member (Dealt with Broken Jaws and Cases of Hospitalizations.

Charity Event Committee

Gaming For Charity & Gereja Bethel Indonesia & Habitat For Humanity Dec 2019 - June 2020

- Worked on attracting Sponsorships,
 Fundraising, Live Streaming Events, Technical Support.
- Missionary Work in Manado and Suka Bumi,
 Volunteered as a Crisis Team (Helping in times of Natural Disasters).
- Raised \$7000 USD for students without school supplies in rural Indonesia.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- Java, HTML/CSS, Python, JavaScript, SQL, Rocky Linux, Graylog
- Critical thinking skills
- Extroverted (Able to work with diverse team structures)
- · Fast learner and adapter
- · Microsoft Office and Adobe suite

CONTACT ME AT

Email: Soebrotom@spu.edu Phone: (206) 532 9210

Addess: 17990 Midvale Ave N Apt 416, Shoreline

WA 98133

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mikhael-bradley-

soebroto